<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>small-business on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/tags/small-business/</link><description>Recent content in small-business on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://apiobuild.com/tags/small-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Set Up Website with Goldfish?</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/blog/how-to-set-up-website-with-goldfish/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/blog/how-to-set-up-website-with-goldfish/</guid><description>The myth under the sea is that goldfish&amp;rsquo;s memory spans only three seconds. apio presents to you a one-page website generator that makes those 3 seconds worth it. A one-page website indicates a website that contains all the information in one HTML page. All the information is kept in one place which makes the navigation easier and allows you to control how you tell your story. In this article, we will show you how to use Goldfish by apio to create a simple website that showcase your works or tell your brand story!</description></item><item><title>Starting an Online Store with Chopin and Instagram</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/blog/starting-an-online-store-with-chopin-and-instagram/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/blog/starting-an-online-store-with-chopin-and-instagram/</guid><description>The first step to start an online business is to create a website. This involves getting a domain, hiring developers, creating contents and more. That’s a lot of work and investment before you can even put your products online. Many small business owners turn to social media (mostly Facebook and Instagram) to build up their brand. It’s free, easy, and most people are already familiar with these platforms. Our online store creator Chopin shares these benefits and can join forces with Instagram to help you create an online store with your Instagram posts.</description></item><item><title>Build a website for your business? What do you need?</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/blog/build-a-website-for-your-business-what-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/blog/build-a-website-for-your-business-what-do-you-need/</guid><description>If you are starting a business in 2020, your first step is almost always to create a website. Though some websites are easier to create than another, an intro-page is as much a website as Facebook. While one couldn&amp;rsquo;t possibly create Facebook with SquareSpace, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to create something simpler that represents your brand on Wix , Wordpress, and many other website builders. Why are people still hire developers when there are website builders?</description></item></channel></rss>