<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Waitress on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</title><link>/tags/waitress/</link><description>Recent content in Waitress on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/waitress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chopin 網路商店設定常見問題</title><link>/blog/troubleshoot-chopin-store-zh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/troubleshoot-chopin-store-zh/</guid><description>&lt;p>設定 &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin&lt;/a> 網路商店的過程中，如果碰到一些小難題、看到錯誤訊息或是哭哭的派大星，不要緊張，可以參考&lt;a href="#checklist" >新手常見錯誤&lt;/a>自行除錯看看！&lt;/p>
&lt;p>常見問題包括&lt;a href="#%e5%9c%96%e7%89%87" >圖片顯示&lt;/a>、&lt;a href="#%e5%95%86%e5%93%81%e7%9b%ae%e9%8c%84%e5%92%8c%e8%a8%82%e5%96%ae" >商品目錄和訂單 google sheet&lt;/a>、&lt;a href="#%e4%bb%98%e6%ac%be%e6%96%b9%e5%bc%8f" >付款方式&lt;/a>等等，也收錄了&lt;a href="#%e5%85%b6%e4%bb%96%e5%95%8f%e9%a1%8c" >其他小問題&lt;/a>。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>如果還是無法解決的話，歡迎直接聯絡我們！可以&lt;a href="mailto:apiobuild@gmail.com">寫信&lt;/a>或是使用 &lt;a href="https://m.me/apiobuild" target="_blank" >Facebook 訊息&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;img src="../../images/blog/chopin-error.png" class="post-img"></description></item><item><title>如何設定 Chopin 網路商店</title><link>/blog/how-to-configure-chopin-store-zh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-configure-chopin-store-zh/</guid><description>&lt;p>建立了 &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin&lt;/a> 商店後，接下來需要 &lt;a href="#%e6%9b%b4%e6%96%b0%e5%95%86%e5%93%81%e7%9b%ae%e9%8c%84" >1) 抽換商品目錄 google sheet 中的範例資料成你想販賣的商品&lt;/a>，並且 &lt;a href="#%e5%ae%a2%e8%a3%bd%e5%8c%96%e4%bd%a0%e7%9a%84%e5%95%86%e5%ba%97" >2) 客製商店外觀和加上其他細節設定&lt;/a>。這篇文章會手把手教你 google sheet 每個儲存格代表的意思，以及所有我們支援的設定，讓你輕鬆完成一個適合自己的商店！&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Something Went Wrong? Troubleshooting Your Chopin Store</title><link>/blog/troubleshoot-chopin-store/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/troubleshoot-chopin-store/</guid><description>&lt;p>We try our best to design a fool-proof onboarding process, but things happen, if you see error messages or Patrick Star crying (hopefully really rare), let us run this &lt;a href="#checklist" >checklist&lt;/a> and troubleshoot together!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also feature some commonly asked questions regarding &lt;a href="#image" >images&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="#google-sheets" >google sheets&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="#payment-method" >payment methods&lt;/a>, and &lt;a href="#and-more" >many more&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/troubleshoot/" target="_blank" >📚 We stop maintaining this troubleshooting guide. Read full content in docs →&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Configure Your Chopin Store</title><link>/blog/how-to-configure-chopin-store/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-configure-chopin-store/</guid><description>&lt;p>After creating your &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin&lt;/a> store, you now need to &lt;a href="https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/product-configuration/" target="_blank" >1) update the catalog google sheet&lt;/a> with your own product information; &lt;a href="https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/store-configuration/" target="_blank" >2) finish setting up your store in Chopin app&lt;/a>, including appearance, social accounts, discount rule, free shipping threshold, etc. In this article, we will breakdown all the google sheet fields as well as explain customization settings. Let us help you create a store tailored for your business needs!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/" target="_blank" >📚 We stop updating this guide. Read full content in docs →&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Create Web Store with Chopin and Waitress</title><link>/blog/how-to-create-web-store-with-apio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-create-web-store-with-apio/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin by apio&lt;/a> is a static online store generator that allows you to configure your online store in just a few clicks. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how you create an online store with google sheet using &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/waitress" target="_blank" >Waitress&lt;/a> (apio&amp;rsquo;s google sheet API microservice). Try now and start selling your products online!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Create an Online Store for FREE with Chopin</title><link>/blog/create-an-online-store-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/create-an-online-store-for-free/</guid><description>Are you looking for a free and easy way to create your online store? We have a solution for you - introducing Chopin by apio: a simple online store creator that allows you to configure your online store with google sheet. It’s a FREE tool with flexibility to customize and integrate with third-party API. No code required - Try now and start selling your products online!
🛍️ Create your store with Chopin in 10mines</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Simple Email Sign Up with Waitress</title><link>/blog/how-to-create-a-simple-email-signup-with-apio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-create-a-simple-email-signup-with-apio/</guid><description>Are you struggling with finding a FREE service to collect emails? Are you overwhelmed by all those fancy features provided by email marketing solutions? In this post, we will show you how to collect email from your website visitors with google sheet. Waitress - apio&amp;rsquo;s google sheet API microservice will help you to build relationship with users in less than 10 minutes and without using email marketing platforms.
📭 See tutorial in docs</description></item><item><title>Collect Email Addresses without Email Marketing Tools</title><link>/blog/collect-email-addresses-without-email-marketing-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/collect-email-addresses-without-email-marketing-tools/</guid><description>Collect emails from website sign-ups is one of the most crucial ways to grow your audience, whether you’re looking to convert subscribers to customers or to directly communicate to your clients. In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to setup easy email sign-up form with google sheet for free on your website.
We built this service after looking into other email marketing platforms (MailChimp, Constant Contacts, OmniSend, etc.), comparing their services, plans, and going through those articles like Five Best Free Email Marketing Services.</description></item></channel></rss>