<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Product-Updates on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</title><link>/tags/product-updates/</link><description>Recent content in Product-Updates on apio | Low Code SaaS Platform</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/product-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fresh New Look for Chopin</title><link>/blog/news-ui-updates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/news-ui-updates/</guid><description>&lt;p>We’ve been working hard on the new &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin&lt;/a> web app. &lt;strong>The updated app helps your customers to find products more easily and resume their unfinished shopping trips seamlessly.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In addition to &lt;a href="#new-layout-better-navigation" >a fresh UI&lt;/a>, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you the following major updates:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#cached-shopping-cart" >Cached Shopping Cart&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#search-product-easily" >Search Function&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#styling-with-markdown" >Text Styling with Markdown&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title>New! Chopin Now Supports More Currencies (plus Other New Features)</title><link>/blog/news-support-more-currencies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/news-support-more-currencies/</guid><description>&lt;p>As we see a greater number of &lt;a href="https://telescope.apiobuild.com/app/chopin" target="_blank" >Chopin&lt;/a> sign-ups are from outside of the U.S., we are expanding our functionalities to better address their business needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These exciting updates include:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#local-currency" >Support Local Currency&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#twitter-and-whatsapp" >Add Twitter and WhatsApp as Contacts&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#collect-on-delivery" >Add Collect on Delivery as a Payment Method&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title>How to Set Up Website with Goldfish?</title><link>/blog/how-to-set-up-website-with-goldfish/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-set-up-website-with-goldfish/</guid><description>The myth under the sea is that goldfish&amp;rsquo;s memory spans only three seconds. apio presents to you a one-page website generator that makes those 3 seconds worth it. A one-page website indicates a website that contains all the information in one HTML page. All the information is kept in one place which makes the navigation easier and allows you to control how you tell your story. In this article, we will show you how to use Goldfish by apio to create a simple website that showcase your works or tell your brand story!</description></item><item><title>How to Add Options to Products for a Chopin Store?</title><link>/blog/how-to-add-options-to-products/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/how-to-add-options-to-products/</guid><description>Are you selling products with multiple size and color options? We bring to you an advanced Chopin store that can showcase several product variations. We promise there won&amp;rsquo;t be complex configuration. Just the same catalog google sheet with few more columns, you will be able to sell clothes with different style and size, handmade craft with various patterns, or cupcakes with multiple flavors, etc. In this tutorial, we will show you how to set up your catalog google sheet to add multiple options to your products.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Post-It: Communication Automation Service</title><link>/blog/introducing-post-it-email-automation-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/introducing-post-it-email-automation-service/</guid><description>Announcing our new service: Post-it - a communication automation service. We wrap various communication APIs in one place. You can send pre-templated messages from your own email address and other social accounts over API (we currently support Gmail) with simple configuration. In this post, we will show you how you can use Post-it with Chopin (apio's online store creator) to send automated order confirmation.
📚 Explore apio docs
Use Case: Automated Order Confirmation Order confirmation is a great way to signal customers that the store has received their orders and remind customers if there&amp;rsquo;s any pending actions (for example: payment confirmation, delivery schedule, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>